ICICI LBRD has disclosed its Q1 results
and there are
no dividend announcements here.
Let's go to their numbers.
Look at the numbers and understand.  Here
all the numbers are in rupees in lakhs.  We will
understand in crores.  First of all we will talk about
their income.  So it was 5851 crores
in the last quarter.  In the same quarter last year,
you saw 5351 cases
and in this quarter, you are seeing an increase of 683 cases.
Friends, if we
understand here in percentage, then on yearly basis you are
seeing a jump of 14% in their revenue
and on quarterly basis you are
seeing a jump of about 4%.  Let us now
talk about how much their total expenses have been.
His expenses in the last quarter were Rs
5435.  In the same quarter last year,
you saw 4850 here.   It has
increased to 5429 in this quarter.   Just
as there was growth in their revenue, a
slight increase is also being seen in expenses.
Let us now talk about
what their total profits are coming out to be.
Friends, in the last quarter,
their profit was seen to be Rs 509 crore.  Last year
in the same quarter you saw 580.
You are seeing an increase in 747s in this quarter.  There
is a jump in both yearly basis and quarterly basis.  If we understand in percentage, then
here we are
seeing a move of approximately 29% on yearly basis.  At the same time, on
quarterly basis, a
huge jump of 46% is being seen here.
You will see it here.  So friends, the
numbers here are looking quite amazing.
Let us now talk about
how the shares look on their earnings?
Because here we will talk about NPA.
So the NPA section has been left blank here.
So we will talk directly on EPS.
In the last quarter,
you saw EPS of ₹10 here.  Last year,
in the same quarter, around ₹12 were seen here.
You are seeing an increase of ₹15 in this quarter.  This is what we are
talking about in Lamsam.  So the numbers are
looking quite amazing here.  Now let's
see what impact they have on the market.
So friends, if you like the video
then please like it.  If this is your first time on the channel, please
subscribe.  See you
in the next video.  Thank you.